{
    "id": "72d4157c833e49b096079f87d6c9baa9",
    "title": "Phrasal verbs",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "1eeea3ef85bb4ca1b41499faadc05be0",
            "title": "Phrasal Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I took him …………………… his brother. They are quite alike.",
                    "description": "To take for is to mistake for another person.",
                    "answers": [
                        "of",
                        "for",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They ……………………… with the best intentions.",
                    "description": "To set out is to start a journey.",
                    "answers": [
                        "set in",
                        "set down",
                        "set out"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The new chairman will …………………………… on 20th January.",
                    "description": "To take over is to assume responsibility.",
                    "answers": [
                        "take out",
                        "take in",
                        "take over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When water was poured on his face, he soon came ………………………",
                    "description": "To come around is to regain consciousness. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "off",
                        "around",
                        "up"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "An orator must be good at getting his message …………………………….",
                    "description": "To get your message across is to convey it. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "across",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is getting ……………………… well in his career.",
                    "description": "To get on is to progress.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "over",
                        "along"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He kept ………………………… asking silly questions.",
                    "description": "To keep on is to continue.",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "out",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The government failed to …………………………… the riots.",
                    "description": "To put down is to crush.",
                    "answers": [
                        "put put",
                        "put down",
                        "put off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They all look ……………………………… him as their leader.",
                    "description": "To look up to somebody is to treat them with respect.",
                    "answers": [
                        "up to",
                        "up",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Once he became successful, he began to look …………………………… his old friends.",
                    "description": "To look down on somebody is to treat them with contempt.",
                    "answers": [
                        "down",
                        "below",
                        "down on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The doctor advised him to abstain …………………………… alcoholic drinks.",
                    "description": "To abstain from is to refrain him.",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "from",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He had promised to lend me some money, but he backed ………………………… later.",
                    "description": "To back out is to withdraw from a promise. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "up",
                        "out",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}